Finding aid to the Classes of 1891-1900 records CA.MS.01022
Smith College Archives
- Class of 1894 Records, 1823-1977; 7.208 linear feet (18 containers)
  - Class of 1894: Chapman, Elizabeth Kimball (Photographs), undated (Box 1485, Folder 17)
  - Class of 1894: Chapman, Marguerite Elisabeth, undated (Box 1485, Folder 18)
  - Class of 1894: Clark, Mary Barnard (Correspondence), 1890; 1892-94; 1898; undated (Box 1485, Folder 19)
  - Class of 1894: Clark, Mary Barnard (Photographs, etc), 1890; 1896; 1900; 1963; undated (Box 1485, Folder 20)
  - Class of 1894: Clark, Mary Barnard (Student Papers), 1892-94; undated (Box 1485, Folder 21)
  - Class of 1894: Clark, Mary Barnard (Student Papers), 1892-93; undated (Box 1485, Folder 22)
  - Class of 1894: Clough, Anna Grace (Correspondence), 1958 (Box 1485, Folder 23)
  - Class of 1894: Covel, Abbie Walker, 1949; undated (Box 1485, Folder 24)
  - Class of 1894: Coyle, Susan Edmond (Photographs), undated (Box 1485, Folder 25)
  - Class of 1894: Davis, Alice Abigail, 1950 (Box 1486, Folder 1)
  - Class of 1894: Davis, Mary Isabella (Account Book, Photographs), 1887-88; 1890-93; undated (Box 1486, Folder 2)
  - Class of 1894: De Ridder, Belle (Correspondence), 1959 (Box 1486, Folder 3)
  - Class of 1894: De Ridder, Belle (Photographs), undated (Box 1486, Folder 4)
  - Class of 1894: Devin, Ethel Wyatt (Correspondence), 1952-59; undated (Box 1486, Folder 5)
  - Class of 1894: Devin, Ethel Wyatt (Photographs), undated (Box 1486, Folder 6)
  - Class of 1894: Dickerman, Elizabeth Street (Photographs), 1910; 1919 (Box 1486, Folder 7)
  - Class of 1894: Dunbar, Olivia Howard (Photographs, Writings), 1903-05; 1907; 1909-11; 1915; 1922; undated (Box 1486, Folder 8)
  - Class of 1894: Dunbar, Olivia Howard (Writings), 1903; 1905; 1907-10; 1913-15; 1919; 1921; 1924 (Box 1486, Folder 9)
  - Class of 1894: Dickerman, Elizabeth Street (Writings), 1917-19; 1921; 1923; undated (Box 1486, Folder 10)
  - Class of 1894: Dustin, Anne Rogers (Photographs), 1893-94 (Box 1486, Folder 11)
  - Class of 1894: Eastman, Mary Bentley (Correspondence), 1958; undated (Box 1487, Folder 1)
  - Class of 1894: Evans, Laura Livingston (Photographs), undated (Box 1487, Folder 2)
  - Class of 1894: Fairbanks, Charlotte (Photographs, etc), 1922; 1932; undated (Box 1487, Folder 3)
  - Class of 1894: Fletcher, Elizabeth Le Baron, 1951; 1967 (Box 1487, Folder 4)
  - Class of 1894: French, Marian Leslie, 1945 (Box 1487, Folder 5)
  - Class of 1894: French, Marian Leslie (Photographs), undated (Box 1487, Folder 6)
  - Class of 1894: Frost, Mary Pepperell (Box 1487, Folder 7)
  - Class of 1894: Frost, Mary Pepperrell (Photographs, Scrapbook), Various dates (Box 1490)
  - Class of 1894: Fuller, Mary Breese (Photographs, etc), 1900; 1902; 1904; 1911; 1915; undated (Box 1487, Folder 8)
  - Class of 1894: Gale, Marion, 1951-52; undated (Box 1487, Folder 9)
  - Class of 1894: Gane, Gertrude (Photographs), undated (Box 1487, Folder 10)
  - Class of 1894: Gane, Gertrude (Correspondence-Index), 1890-1894 (Box 1487, Folder 11)
  - Class of 1894: Gane, Gertrude (Correspondence-Sept-Oct 1890) (Box 1487, Folder 12)
  - Class of 1894: Gane, Gertrude (Correspondence-Nov 1890-Mar 1892), 1890-1892 (Box 1487, Folder 13)
  - Class of 1894: Gane, Gertrude (Correspondence-May 1892-Sept 1893), 1892-1893 (Box 1487, Folder 14)
  - Class of 1894: Gane, Gertrude (Correspondence-Oct-Dec 1893) (Box 1487, Folder 15)
  - Class of 1894: Gane, Gertrude (Correspondence-Jan-Mar 1894) (Box 1487, Folder 16)
  - Class of 1894: Gane, Gertrude (Correspondence-Apr-Jun 1894) (Box 1487, Folder 17)
  - Class of 1894: Gane, Gertrude (Typed Copies of Correspondence-Aug-Oct 1890) (Box 1487, Folder 18)
  - Class of 1894: Gane, Gertrude (Typed Copies of Correspondence-Nov 1890-Jan 1892), 1890-1892 (Box 1487, Folder 19)
  - Class of 1894: Gane, Gertrude (Typed Copies of Correspondence-Mar 1892-Oct 1893), 1892-1893 (Box 1487, Folder 20)
  - Class of 1894: Gane, Gertrude (Typed Copies of Correspondence-Nov 1893-Jan 1894), 1893-1894 (Box 1487, Folder 21)
  - Class of 1894: Gane, Gertrude (Typed Copies of Correspondence-Feb-Jun 1894) (Box 1487, Folder 22)
  - Class of 1894: Gane, Gertrude (Course Notes), 1893 (Box 1487, Folder 23)
  - Class of 1894: Gane, Gertrude (Memorabilia book), Various dates (Box 1491)
  - Class of 1894: Gane, Gertrude (photo album) (Box 1491.2)
  - Class of 1894: Gane, Gertrude (Index, Correspondence, Photographs, Class Notes) (Box 1491.1)
  - Class of 1894: Graves, Katherine Olive (Photographs), 1914; 1917 (Box 1487, Folder 24)
  - Class of 1894: Greenough, Clara Mary, 1951-54; 1957; 1959; undated (Box 1487, Folder 25)
  - Class of 1894: Greenough, Clara Mary (Certificates), 1918-19; 1923-24; 1930-31; 1934 (Box 1487, Folder 26)
  - Class of 1894: Hall, Alice Evangeline (Box 1487, Folder 27)
  - Class of 1894: Hall, Alice Evangeline (Biography and Genealogy), 1886; 1896; 1917; 1948; 1955; 1977; undated (Box 1492, Folder 1)
  - Class of 1894: Hall, Alice Evangeline (Biog.-Miscellaneous), 1891-92; 1898; 1921-22; undated (Box 1492, Folder 2)
  - Class of 1894: Hall, Alice Evangeline (Bird study and Audubon Society of Rhode Island), 1939; 1942-43; 1949; 1953; undated (Box 1492, Folder 3)
  - Class of 1894: Hall, Alice Evangeline (Correspondence), 1885-86; 1910; 1933; 1940-41; undated (Box 1492, Folder 4)
  - Class of 1894: Hall, Alice Evangeline (Education-Lyndon Institute, 1887), 1886-87 (Box 1492, Folder 5)
  - Class of 1894: Hall, Alice Evangeline (Education-Smith College: Course Lecture Notes), 1890-92; undated (Box 1492, Folder 6)
  - Class of 1894: Hall, Alice Evangeline (Education-Smith College: Course Lecture Notes-English Literature), 1890; undated (Box 1492, Folder 7)
  - Class of 1894: Hall, Alice Evangeline (Drawings), 1892; undated (Box 1492, Folder 8)
  - Class of 1894: Hall, Alice Evangeline (Manuscripts), 1909; 1912; 1925; undated (Box 1492, Folder 9)
  - Class of 1894: Hall, Alice Evangeline (Manuscripts-Joel Dunbar), undated (Box 1492, Folder 10)
  - Class of 1894: Hall, Alice Evangeline (Photographs), 1908; undated (Box 1492, Folder 11)
  - Class of 1894: Hall, Alice Evangeline (Publications), 1888-89; 1901; 1907; 1943 (Box 1492, Folder 12)
  - Class of 1894: Hammond, Juliet (Correspondence), 1954 (Box 1487, Folder 28)
  - Class of 1894: Harkness, Edith Alice, 1951; undated (Box 1487, Folder 29)
  - Class of 1894: Hart, Helen Marguerite (Photographs), 1893-94; undated (Box 1487, Folder 30)
  - Class of 1894: Hartwell, Mary Ann, 1946 (Box 1487, Folder 31)
  - Class of 1894: Hartwell, Mary Ann (Photographs, etc), 1913-15; 1922-23; 1925; 1939; 1943; undated (Box 1487, Folder 32)
  - Class of 1894: Herrick, A(da) Elizabeth (Photographs, etc), 1823; 1826; 1843; 1845-46; 1867; 1870; 1873; 1905; 1914; 1919; 1922; 1945; undated (Box 1487, Folder 33)
  - Class of 1894: Hubbard, Alice Clark (Correspondence), 1954; undated (Box 1487, Folder 34)
  - Class of 1894: Hubbard, Alice Clark (Photographs), undated (Box 1487, Folder 35)
  - Class of 1894: Humphrey, Mary King (Box 1487, Folder 36)
  - Class of 1894: Humphrey, Mary King (photo album) (Box 1491.2)
  - Class of 1894: Ingram, Lucy Belle, 1911 (Box 1487, Folder 37)
  - Class of 1894: Johnson, Eleanor Hope (Photographs, etc), 1891; 1902; 1911; 1920; 1927; 1935-36; 1942-45; 1947; 1949-51; 1953-55; 1963-64; undated (Box 1487, Folder 38)
  - Class of 1894: Jones, Ellen Permelia, 1944 (Box 1487, Folder 39)
  - Class of 1894: Jones, Ellen Permelia (Photographs), undated (Box 1487, Folder 40)
  - Class of 1894: Kimball, Martha Hayward (Photographs), undated (Box 1487, Folder 41)
  - Class of 1894: Lamb, Lucy Inez (Correspondence), 1950-59 (Box 1488, Folder 1)
  - Class of 1894: Lamb, Lucy Inez (Photographs), 1959; undated (Box 1488, Folder 2)
  - Class of 1894: Lambert, Helen Bordman (Photographs), undated (Box 1488, Folder 3)
  - Class of 1894: Leach, Alice Lydia (Correspondence), undated (Box 1488, Folder 4)
  - Class of 1894: Learned, Agnes Wakefield (Photographs), 1888; undated (Box 1488, Folder 5)
  - Class of 1894: Leighton, Emma Elizabeth, 1899; 1904-05; 1908 (Box 1488, Folder 6)
  - Class of 1894: Lewis, Mary Delia (Box 1488, Folder 7)
  - Class of 1894: Lockwood, Jeanne Julia (Correspondence), 1951-52; 1954; undated (Box 1488, Folder 8)
  - Class of 1894: Lockwood, Jeanne Julia (Photographs, etc), 1954; undated (Box 1488, Folder 9)
  - Class of 1894: Lyall, Katherine E. (Correspondence-Sept 26, 1890-May 17, 1891), 1890-1891 (Box 1488, Folder 10)
  - Class of 1894: Lynch, Caroline Vinia (Photographs, etc), 1926; undated (Box 1488, Folder 11)
  - Class of 1894: McMahan, Una, 1906-07; 1909 (Box 1488, Folder 12)
  - Class of 1894: Mann, Clausine, 1950; undated (Box 1488, Folder 13)
  - Class of 1894: Mansfield, Elizabeth Langley (Correspondence, etc), 1954 (Box 1488, Folder 14)
  - Class of 1894: Mansfield, Elizabeth Langley (Photographs), undated (Box 1488, Folder 15)
  - Class of 1894: Mason, Martha (Correspondence), 1949-51; undated (Box 1488, Folder 16)
  - Class of 1894: Mason, Martha (Photographs), 1890-91; 1893-94; 1917-19 (Box 1488, Folder 17)
  - Class of 1894: Mead, Stella Baham (Correspondence), 1954 (Box 1488, Folder 18)
  - Class of 1894: Merrill, Georgiana (Photographs, etc), 1895; 1916; 1927; 1929; 1945; undated (Box 1488, Folder 19)
  - Class of 1894: Merriman, Mabel Lilian (Photographs, etc), 1920-22; undated (Box 1488, Folder 20)
  - Class of 1894: Moon, Elizabeth Laetitia, 1900-01; 1946 (Box 1488, Folder 21)
  - Class of 1894: Moon, Elizabeth Laetitia (Photographs), undated (Box 1488, Folder 22)
  - Class of 1894: Moore, Mabel Reynolds, 1934; 1938; 1950; undated (Box 1488, Folder 23)
  - Class of 1894: Morse, Anna Gertrude (Correspondence), 1954 (Box 1488, Folder 24)
  - Class of 1894: Noyes, Bertha Lizette (Photographs), 1896; undated (Box 1488, Folder 25)
  - Class of 1894: Oakes, Julia Anna (Photographs) (Box 1488, Folder 26)
  - Class of 1894: Parrish, Margaret Louise (Correspondence), 1951 (Box 1488, Folder 27)
  - Class of 1894: Paul, Anne Marie, 1894-95; 1951; undated (Box 1488, Folder 28)
  - Class of 1894: Peck, Teresina (Correspondence), 1906; 1945-46 (Box 1488, Folder 29)
  - Class of 1894: Peck, Teresina (Photographs, etc), 1938; undated (Box 1488, Folder 30)
  - Class of 1894: Perkins, Helen (Correspondence), 1897; 1949; 1952; 1956; 1958-59; undated (Box 1488, Folder 31)
  - Class of 1894: Pickering, Minnie Maud, 1948 (Box 1488, Folder 32)
  - Class of 1894: Pickering, Minnie Maud (Photographs), undated (Box 1488, Folder 33)
  - Class of 1894: Platt, Ada Susan (Correspondence), 1955 (Box 1488, Folder 34)
  - Class of 1894: Platt, Ada Susan (Photographs), undated (Box 1488, Folder 35)
  - Class of 1894: Platt, Clara Boardman (Photographs), undated (Box 1488, Folder 36)
  - Class of 1894: Pratt, Sarah Marie, 1949 (Box 1488, Folder 37)
  - Class of 1894: Pratt, Sarah Marie (Photographs), 1892; undated (Box 1488, Folder 38)
  - Class of 1894: Prouty, Mable Lucretia (Photographs), 1893-94 (Box 1488, Folder 39)
  - Class of 1894: Putney, Mary Phillips (Photographs) (Box 1488, Folder 40)
  - Class of 1894: Putney, Mary Phillips (Scrapbook) (Box 1495.1)
  - Class of 1894: Reynolds, Harriet Lyman (Correspondence), 1936; undated (Box 1488, Folder 41)
  - Class of 1894: Rice, Lillian Ballance (Photographs), 1893-94; 1947; undated (Box 1488, Folder 42)
  - Class of 1894: Rice, Lillian Balance (Scrapbooks), Various dates (Box 1493)
  - Class of 1894: Richardson, Belle (Photographs), 1950; undated (Box 1488, Folder 43)
  - Class of 1894: Richardson, Belle (photo album) (Box 1491.2)
  - Class of 1894: Richardson, Mary Lilias (Box 1488, Folder 44)
  - Class of 1894: Robbins, Alice Emily (Photographs), undated (Box 1488, Folder 45)
  - Class of 1894: Rogers, Annie (Correspondence), 1952; 1954; undated (Box 1488, Folder 46)
  - Class of 1894: Rogers, Annie (Photographs), 1893 (Box 1488, Folder 47)
  - Class of 1894: Ruger, Harriet Marsh, 1944 (Box 1488, Folder 48)
  - Class of 1894: Rugg, Harriet Alice (Photographs), undated (Box 1488, Folder 49)
  - Class of 1894: Sanford, Stella De Land (Correspondence), 1954 (Box 1489, Folder 1)
  - Class of 1894: Schermerhorn, Rena (Photographs), 1890 (Box 1489, Folder 2)
  - Class of 1894: Scott, Mary Stuart (Photographs) (Box 1489, Folder 3)
  - Class of 1894: Searl, Mabel Darrow (Correspondence), 1952 (Box 1489, Folder 4)
  - Class of 1894: Searl, Mabel Darrow (Photographs), 1895; undated (Box 1489, Folder 5)
  - Class of 1894: Seelye, Mabel, 1872 (Box 1489, Folder 6)
  - Class of 1894: Sherrill, Grace Munger (Photographs), 1892; undated (Box 1489, Folder 7)
  - Class of 1894: Sherwood, Tirzah Lovejoy (Photographs), undated (Box 1489, Folder 8)
  - Class of 1894: Smith, Abigail May (Photographs), 1891 (Box 1489, Folder 9)
  - Class of 1894: Smith, Alice Abigail, 1892; 1949; undated (Box 1489, Folder 10)
  - Class of 1894: Smith, Grace Angeline (Correspondence), 1950-51; undated (Box 1489, Folder 11)
  - Class of 1894: Smith, Grace Angeline (Photographs), 1894-95; undated (Box 1489, Folder 12)
  - Class of 1894: Swett, Edith Josephine (Photographs), 1893 (Box 1489, Folder 13)
  - Class of 1894: Taft, Anna Gleason (Photographs) (Box 1489, Folder 14)
  - Class of 1894: Thompson, Caroline Lee Hualani, 1937 (Box 1489, Folder 15)
  - Class of 1894: Wakelin, Elizabeth, undated (Box 1489, Folder 16)
  - Class of 1894: Walton, Mabel Lilian, 1948 (Box 1489, Folder 17)
  - Class of 1894: Warburton, Cora Isabel (Correspondence, etc), undated (Box 1489, Folder 18)
  - Class of 1894: Warburton, Cora Isabel (Photographs), undated (Box 1489, Folder 19)
  - Class of 1894: Ware, Katharine (Bookplate), 1947-49; 1957 (Box 1489, Folder 20)
  - Class of 1894: Ware, Katherine (Photographs, etc), 1917; undated (Box 1489, Folder 21)
  - Class of 1894: Watters, Bertha Alice (Correspondence), 1900; 1948; 1952-54; 1959; undated (Box 1489, Folder 22)
  - Class of 1894: Watters, Bertha Alice (Photographs, etc), 1896; undated (Box 1489, Folder 23)
  - Class of 1894: Webster, Letitia / Whiton, Helen Isabel (Photo album, Scrapbook), Various dates (Box 1494)
  - Class of 1894: Wenham, Grace Putnam, 1951 (Box 1489, Folder 24)
  - Class of 1894: Wenham, Grace Putnam (Photographs), undated (Box 1489, Folder 25)
  - Class of 1894: Whiton, Helen Isabel (Box 1489, Folder 26)
  - Class of 1894: Wilder, Bertha Frances (Photographs), undated (Box 1489, Folder 27)
  - Class of 1894: Wilkinson, Charlotte Coffyn (Box 1489, Folder 28)
  - Class of 1894: Willard, E(lisa) May (Photographs, etc), 1917; undated (Box 1489, Folder 29)
  - Class of 1894: Williams, Sarah Holbrook (Photographs), 1893-94; undated (Box 1489, Folder 30)
  - Class of 1894: Wood, Alice Dewey (Photographs), 1891; undated (Box 1489, Folder 31)
  - Class of 1894: Wyman, Helen Lydia, undated (Box 1489, Folder 32)
  - Johnson, Eleanor Hope (plaque) (Box 1495.2)
- Class of 1895 Records, 1891-1962; 11.604 linear feet (23 containers)
  The Class of 1895 was the seventeenth entering class and the seventeenth graduating class of Smith College.
  The Class of 1895 records, 1891-1960, contain materials describing the history and activities of the Class of 1895, including materials from commencement, reunions, senior dramatics, and other important events. Types of materials include photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, and other memorabilia.
  Individual biographical files are also available, and often include photographs, photo albums, newspaper clippings, letters and correspondences, and class notes.
  - Baccalaureate, 1895 (Box 1496, Folder 1)
  - Basketball Team, 1893 (Box 1496, Folder 2)
  - Commencement, 1895 (Box 1496, Folder 3)
  - Commencement Music, 1895 (Box 1496, Folder 4)
  - Commencement Photographs, 1895 (Box 1496, Folder 5)
  - Commencement Speaker, 1895 (Box 1496, Folder 6)
  - Class Dramatics, 1895 (Box 1496, Folder 7)
  - Groups, 1891-1895 (Box 1496, Folder 8)
  - Groups, 1891-1895 (Box 1496, Folder 9)
  - History, 1891-1895 (Box 1496, Folder 10)
  - Ivy Day, 1895 (Box 1496, Folder 11)
  - Ivy Day Photographs, 1895 (Box 1496, Folder 12)
  - Junior Prom, 1894 (Box 1496, Folder 13)
  - Junior Prom, 1894 (Box 1496, Folder 14)
  - Junior Reception, 1894 (Box 1496, Folder 15)
  - Junior Ushers, 1894 (Box 1496, Folder 16)
  - Class Letters, 1953-1962 (Box 1496, Folder 17)
  - Organizations, 1895 (Box 1496, Folder 18)
  - Songs, 1893-1895 (Box 1497, Folder 1)
  - Seat, 1962 (Box 1497, Folder 2)
  - Senior Drama, 1895 (Box 1497, Folder 3)
  - Senior Party at Morris House, 1895 (Box 1497, Folder 4)
  - Sophomore Reception, 1894 (Box 1497, Folder 5)
  - Class Supper, 1895 (Box 1497, Folder 6)
  - Student Rooms, 1895 (Box 1497, Folder 7)
  - Reunions, 1896 (Box 1498, Folder 1)
  - Reunions, 1900 (Box 1498, Folder 2)
  - Reunions, 1905 (Box 1498, Folder 3)
  - Reunions, 1915 (Box 1498, Folder 4)
  - Reunions, 1920 (Box 1498, Folder 5)
  - Reunions, 1925 (Box 1498, Folder 6)
  - Reunions, 1935 (Box 1498, Folder 7)
  - Reunions, 1940 (Box 1498, Folder 8)
  - Reunions, 1945 (Box 1498, Folder 9)
  - Reunions, 1950 (Box 1498, Folder 10)
  - Reunions, 1951 (Box 1498, Folder 11)
  - Reunions, 1952 (Box 1498, Folder 12)
  - Reunions, 1955 (Box 1498, Folder 13)
  - Reunions, 1960 (Box 1498, Folder 14)
  - Reunions, undated (Box 1498, Folder 15)
  - Reunion Photographs, 1896-1960 (Box 1498, Folder 16)
  - Reunion Songs, undated (Box 1498, Folder 17)
  - Senior Dramatics, 1895 (Box 1499, Folder 1)
  - Senior Dramatics, 1897 (Box 1499, Folder 2)
  - Senior Dramatics, 1897 (Box 1499, Folder 3)
  - Senior Dramatics Photographs, 1895 (Box 1499, Folder 4)
  - Senior Dramatics Photographs, 1895 (Box 1499, Folder 5)
  - Senior Dramatics Photographs, 1895 (Box 1499, Folder 6)
  - Senior Dramatics Photographs, 1895 (Box 1499, Folder 7)
  - Individuals A-E (Box 1500)
  - Individuals F-G (Box 1501)
  - Individuals H (Box 1502)
  - Individuals I-O (Box 1503)
  - Individuals P-Wh (Box 1504)
  - Individuals Wi-Z (Box 1505)
  - Cummings, Mabel Homer (photo album) (Box 1507.1)
  - Fuller, Caroline Macomber (Scrapbook) (Box 1506)
  - Goodwin, Maria Bangs (photo album) (Box 1507.1)
  - Harrington, Anna Louise (photo albums) (Box 1507.2)
  - Jackson, Mary Craig-Esse (photo album) (Box 1507)
  - Jackson, Mary Craig-Essie (photo album) (Box 1507.2)
  - Kendall, Lydia Williams (journals and photo album) (Box 1508)
  - Kendall, Lydia Williams (autograph book) (Box 1508.1)
  - Lewis (Day), Elizabeth Dike (typescript autobiography, vol. I & II) (Box 1509)
  - Lewis, Mary Pratt (photo album) (Box 1507)
  - Melcher, Mary Merwin (photo albums) (Box 1510.1)
  - Nichols, Eleanor Hunnewell (scrapbook) (Box 1511)
  - Pratt, Elsie Seelye (photo album) (Box 1511)
  - Richards, Alice Maud (photo album) (Box 1513.1)
  - Smith, Bertha Harriet (photo album) (Box 1513.1)
  - Wells, Marguerite Milton (photo album) (Box 1513.2)
  - Wilkin, Josephine Dunlap (correspondence), 1891-09-1895-09 (Box 1512, Box 1513)
  - Unidentified (photo album) (Box 1507)
- Class of 1896 Records, 1892-1961; 10.458 linear feet (17 containers)
  The Class of 1896 was the eighteenth entering class and the eighteenth graduating class of Smith College.
  The Class of 1896 records, 1892-1961, contain materials describing the history and activities of the Class of 1896, including materials from commencement, reunions, senior dramatics, and other important events. Types of materials include photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, and other memorabilia.
  - Baccalaureate Service, 1896 (Box 1514, Folder 1)
  - Class History, 1896 (Box 1514, Folder 2)
  - Class Secretary Correspondence, 1960-1961 (Box 1514, Folder 3)
  - Commencement, 1896 (Box 1514, Folder 4)
  - Commencement Photos, 1896 (Box 1514, Folder 5)
  - Commencement Music, 1896 (Box 1514, Folder 6)
  - Commencement Speaker, 1896 (Box 1514, Folder 7)
  - Freshman Frolic, 1892 (Box 1514, Folder 8)
  - Groups, 1892-1896 (Box 1514, Folder 9)
  - Ivy Day, 1896 (Box 1514, Folder 10)
  - Ivy Day Photos, 1896 (Box 1514, Folder 11)
  - Junior Reception given by Class of 1897, 1896 (Box 1514, Folder 12)
  - Junior Prom, 1895 (Box 1514, Folder 13)
  - Junior Ushers, 1895 (Box 1514, Folder 14)
  - Letters, 1896-1940 (Box 1514, Folder 15)
  - Organizations, 1896 (Box 1514, Folder 16)
  - Publications, 1916 (Box 1514, Folder 17)
  - Senior Reception, 1896 (Box 1514, Folder 18)
  - Sophomore Reception, 1892 (Box 1514, Folder 19)
  - Songs, undated (Box 1514, Folder 20)
  - Class Supper, 1896 (Box 1514, Folder 21)
  - Reunions: photographs, 1906-1941 (Box 1515, Folder 1)
  - Reunions, 1896-1916 (Box 1515, Folder 2)
  - Reunions: Decennial, 1906 (Box 1515, Folder 3)
  - Reunions, 1911 (Box 1515, Folder 4)
  - Reunions: Sophia Smith Homestead, 1916 (Box 1515, Folder 5)
  - Reunions, 1916 (Box 1515, Folder 6)
  - Reunions, 1921 (Box 1515, Folder 7)
  - Reunions, 1931 (Box 1515, Folder 8)
  - Reunions, 1936 (Box 1515, Folder 9)
  - Reunions, 1941 (Box 1515, Folder 10)
  - Reunions, 1946 (Box 1515, Folder 11)
  - Reunions, 1951 (Box 1515, Folder 12)
  - Reunions, 1956 (Box 1515, Folder 13)
  - Reunions: Songs, undated (Box 1515, Folder 14)
  - Reunions: Memorabilia, undated (Box 1515, Folder 15)
  - Senior Dramatics, 1896 (Box 1516, Folder 1)
  - Senior Dramatics: Photographs, 1896 (Box 1516, Folder 2)
  - Senior Dramatics: Photographs, 1896 (Box 1516, Folder 3)
  - Senior Dramatics: Photographs, 1896 (Box 1516, Folder 4)
  - Senior Dramatics: Photographs, 1896 (Box 1516, Folder 5)
  - Senior Dramatics: Photographs, 1896 (Box 1516, Folder 6)
  - Costumes (Box 1515.1)
  - Individuals A-D (Box 1517)
  - Individuals E-Lea (Box 1518)
  - Individuals Leb-O (Box 1518.1)
  - Individuals P-Z (Box 1519)
  - Adams, Isabel Fay (photo albums) (Box 1520.1)
  - Betts, Emily Julia (photo albums) (Box 1520)
  - Burnham, Clara Avery (photo album) (Box 1520.1)
  - Curtiss, Maude Somers (photo album) (Box 1521)
  - Keller, Maria Louise (photo album) (Box 1520.2)
  - Lillibridge, Grace Rie (scrapbook) (Box 1522)
  - Lloyd, Anna Mary (photo album) (Box 1520.1)
  - Morey, Charlotte Frances (photo album) (Box 1520.2)
  - Reed, Mabel Florence (scrapbooks) (Box 1524, Box 1523)
  - Smith, Emeline Cavarly (scrapbook) (Box 1524.2)
  - Wood, Georgia (Box 1524.1)
- Class of 1897 Records, 1893-1967; 20.062 linear feet (39 containers)
  The Class of 1897 was the nineteenth entering class and the nineteenth graduating class of Smith College.
  The Class of 1897 records, 1893-1967, contain materials describing the history and activities of the Class of 1897, including materials from commencement, reunions, senior dramatics, and other important events. Types of materials include photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, letters, and other memorabilia.
  Individual biographical files are also available, and often include photographs, photo albums, newspaper clippings, letters and correspondences, scrap books and class notes.
  - Baccalaureate Service, 1897 (Box 1525, Folder 1)
  - Collation and Alumnae Tea, 1897 (Box 1525, Folder 2)
  - Commencement, 1897 (Box 1525, Folder 3)
  - Commencement: Photos, 1897 (Box 1525, Folder 4)
  - Commencement: Music, 1897 (Box 1525, Folder 5)
  - Class History, 1893-1920's (Box 1525, Folder 6)
  - Freshman Grind by Class of 1896, undated (Box 1525, Folder 7)
  - Groups, 1893-1897 (Box 1525, Folder 8)
  - Groups, 1893-1897 (Box 1525, Folder 9)
  - Ivy Day, 1897 (Box 1525, Folder 10)
  - Ivy Day: Photos, 1897 (Box 1525, Folder 11)
  - Junior Prom, 1896 (Box 1525, Folder 12)
  - Junior Reception given by Class of 1898, 1896 (Box 1525, Folder 13)
  - Junior Ushers, 1896 (Box 1525, Folder 14)
  - Class Secretary's Correspondence, 1957-1963 (Box 1526, Folder 1)
  - Photographs: Groups, 1895 (Box 1526, Folder 2)
  - Class Letters, 1919-1967 (Box 1526, Folder 3)
  - Pins, 1907 (Box 1526, Folder 4)
  - Secretary's Report, 1893-1913 (Box 1526, Folder 5)